[
  {
    "question": "Pick A Genre",
    "answers": "Hip Hop"
  },
  {
    "question": "Pick A Genre",
    "answers": "Country"
  },
  {
    "question": "Pick A Genre",
    "answers": "Rock"
  },
  {
    "question": "Pick A Genre",
    "answers": "Pop"
  },

  {
    "question": "Pick A Decade",
    "answers": "80's"
  },
  {
    "question": "Pick A Decade",
    "answers": "90's"
  },
  {
    "question": "Pick A Decade",
    "answers": "2000's"
  },
  {
    "question": "Pick A Decade",
    "answers": "Presents"
  },

  {
    "question": "Pick A Mood",
    "answers": "Chill"
  },
  {
    "question": "Pick A Mood",
    "answers": "study"
  },
  {
    "question": "Pick A Mood",
    "answers": "workout"
  },
  {
    "question": "Pick A Mood",
    "answers": "Depressed"
  }
]